<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Transforming cyber security risks into meaningful business terms. on Cyber Risk Quant</title>
    <link>https://CyberRiskQuant.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Transforming cyber security risks into meaningful business terms. on Cyber Risk Quant</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>DAH@CyberRiskQuant.com (Duncan Hart)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>DAH@CyberRiskQuant.com (Duncan Hart)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://CyberRiskQuant.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How much should we be spending on cybersecurity?</title>
      <link>https://CyberRiskQuant.com/posts/howmuchtospend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:26:40 +1000</pubDate>
      <author>DAH@CyberRiskQuant.com (Duncan Hart)</author>
      <guid>https://CyberRiskQuant.com/posts/howmuchtospend/</guid>
      <description>And behind that questions there is usually a deeper executive concern about whether they are under-spending or over-spending.
No CEO wants to be seen as reckless and allow unnecessary risk, but at the same time no one CEO wants to be seen wasting budget that could be spent on revenue generating functions. And it is this tension that makes the above question so commonplace.
Let me know if you are interested in learning how I answer the question: duncan@cyberriskquant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are the purposes of cyber security performance measurement?</title>
      <link>https://CyberRiskQuant.com/posts/purposeperformance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 10:26:40 +1000</pubDate>
      <author>DAH@CyberRiskQuant.com (Duncan Hart)</author>
      <guid>https://CyberRiskQuant.com/posts/purposeperformance/</guid>
      <description>The purpose of cyber security measurement is severalfold. We know that there are a number of important purposes for cyber security performance measurement that serve the following:
Accountability – are you doing what should be doing, at the levels you should, with the right quality.
Transparency about results – are you achieving what you should be achieving, to what extent, and for whom?
Value for money – are you achieving results in the most cost-effective manner?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What constitutes cyber security performance?</title>
      <link>https://CyberRiskQuant.com/posts/problemstatement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 10:26:40 +1000</pubDate>
      <author>DAH@CyberRiskQuant.com (Duncan Hart)</author>
      <guid>https://CyberRiskQuant.com/posts/problemstatement/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re going to have a fighting chance of being successful then you need to start with &amp;lsquo;what is performance?&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;Performance&amp;rsquo; is often used as an inclusive term for the routine measurement of inputs, activities, outputs, outcomes and/or impacts of an intervention, for example a project, program, collection of activities or a policy. The emphasis here is on regularly collecting a set of data to determine where improvements can be made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hardest questions</title>
      <link>https://CyberRiskQuant.com/be-prepared/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 04:52:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>DAH@CyberRiskQuant.com (Duncan Hart)</author>
      <guid>https://CyberRiskQuant.com/be-prepared/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NodeJS</title>
      <link>https://CyberRiskQuant.com/partners/netlifycms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 05:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>DAH@CyberRiskQuant.com (Duncan Hart)</author>
      <guid>https://CyberRiskQuant.com/partners/netlifycms/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://CyberRiskQuant.com/about/duncanhart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>DAH@CyberRiskQuant.com (Duncan Hart)</author>
      <guid>https://CyberRiskQuant.com/about/duncanhart/</guid>
      <description>Duncan Hart is the Founder and Managing Partner of Cyber Risk Quant, a niche specialist in cyber security strategy, performance and risk.
With 25 years experience in technology, information and cyber security industry, including 10 years based in Asia Pacific, Europe and North America, Duncan has been responsible for handling some of the most challenging cyber security issues in both the private and public sectors. Prior to Cyber Risk Quant, Duncan spent several years with BHP, Bank of England, Vodafone Group and QinetiQ.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>